JASON CHOW

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Team member with over 6 years of experience in retail at Coles, an apprentice electrician and a Gym staff member. Excellent at resolving problems, improving customer satisfaction and driving overall operational improvements. Dedicated in team-based settings stepped into any role and producing consistent, high quality work Eager to learn to work efficient and effectively.

Efficient and punctual Gym Attendant with team orientation and creativity. Adjusting equipment and assisting customers with various tasks necessary to enhance customer experience. Versatile employee willing to fulfill widely varying roles as necessary to facilitate smooth operations of gym facility.

WORK HISTORY

Bakery Team Member, 07/2016 - 01/08/2022

Coles, Forestville, NSW

- -Served customers daily with bakery products, and professional and effective customer service
- -Learned all required tasks quickly to maximize performance
- -Cleaned and maintained kitchen equipment and oven
- -Investigated and resolved customer complaints to foster satisfaction
- -Received incoming calls and messages and addressed phone requests
- -Established and maintained positive customer relationships
- -Kept work areas clean, organized and safe to promote efficiency and team safety - Inspected bound and outbound products for compliance with established industry standards, company policies and procedures
- Arranged bakery displays to showcase baked goods, cakes and pies to drive product sales.
- Packaged customer purchases with care and strong organizational skills to facilitate easy carrying and prevent product shifting.

Gym Staff Member, 04/2021 - 08/2022

Forest 24/7 Fitness, Forestville, NSW

Enforced rules and held customers accountable for not following



Forestville, NSW 2087



041-482-2157



jasonblu123@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Exceeding Customer Expectations
- Building Customer Loyalty
- Safety and Cleanliness Standards
- Customer Service
- Stocking
- Motivated team worker
- Goal-oriented
- Customer-oriented
- Quick learner
- Positive and friendly
- Employee relations

Phlebotomist - 1/08/2022 - current

(transferred from Sydney to Melbourne company)

- -Identifying patients via ID, medical record or other means.
- -Drawing blood using needles and other equipment.
- -Labelling samples correctly and send them for testing.
- -Run various tests and work in a fast paced, team environment with customer service excellence

gym regulations.

- Sold memberships and personal training sessions to new customers.
- Posted information on gym hours and upcoming events, maintaining consistent communication with patrons.
- Serviced complex equipment quickly to minimize wait times for specific machines.
- Learning how to manage and run a gym, building relationships with the community and maintaining business procedures

Apprentice Electrician, 02/2020 - 07/2020

Dragon Fire Services, Sydney, NSW

Assisted fully licensed electricians in installing fire alarms, wiring and other components into installing electrical products at jobs

- Organized materials and tools in to maintain clean and neat work areas.
- Worked under supervision of Journeyman Electrician to learn trade and develop electrical knowledge.

EDUCATION

Killarney Heights High School - Killarney Heights

Fitness, 2018

Australian Institute of Fitness - St Leonards, NSW

CERTIFICATIONS

Master Trainer at Australian Institute of Fitness
CERT IV in fitness
Master Trainer

HOBBIES

I Love music I love to train at the gym,

I love the sport of boxing,

I love to hang out with friends,

I love food! I love shopping,

I love to create, Inspire, Motivate, and learn